

Misha Demidenko

• Warsaw, Poland

Prefer to work remotely

- @allwellnow
- in mishademidenko
- +48 507243511

Core Skills

- Swift and iOS SDK
- 🙀 Frameworks
- **EQ**

EQ

Advanced

- communicative and listening skills
- Ability to acceptcriticism and feedback

Self decision-

 making and quick adaptation

Languages

- English Professional working proficiency
- Russian Native proficiency

Education

iOS Developer

Psychology in Business

iOS Developer

Summary

Hello! I'm a junior iOS Developer with a strong Psychological and EQ background, and a passion to solve problems and achieve results and goals. Nothing motivates me more than complicated tasks with an observable result upon completion. I believe that my values and previous experience can help both growing and stable companies in their journey further

Most learned skills:

- Swift, Xcode, UIKit
- Storyboards, Auto Layout
- UserDefaults
- CoreML, CreateML

Mid-learned skills:

- Networking (JSON), API Integration
- Alamofire
- Core Data, Realm
- Cocoa Touch
- Source Control

Less (but still) learned skills:

- Firebase
- ARKit
- CoreLocation

Projects

- Intermittent Fasting App available on the AppStore
- Stocks Prediction App with Twitter API
- Weather App with CoreLocation
- ToDo App with Realm
- Bill + Tip split App

Detailed portfolio available on GitHub:



github link

Experience

iOS Developer (Dec 2022 - Feb 2023)

Self-funded

After 5 months of learning, I've decided to write a complete project to solidify my knowledge and gain new skills in a practical environment

Result:

Intermittent Fasting App, available on the AppStore

Detailed information on this and other projects of mine you can find in my portfolio using the link above

Marketing Generalist (Mar 2022 - Aug 2022)

Gold's Yacht Company, Dubai, UAE

Besides core Marketing responsibilities on this job, an important point to mention is:

 Outsource teams management - management of 3 teams, processes optimization, creation and control of goals and KPIs for each team

As a major result, I consider establishing analytics and report systems with outsource teams as well as 15% average growth on marketing channels

Education

iOS Developer (Aug 2022 - Dec 2022)

Self-taught with courses, professional literature, and documentation

Master of Psychology, Psychology in Business (Sep 2019 - Jun 2021)

National Research University «Higher School of Economics», Moscow